好的下一个问题
All right, next problem.
我有重复的问题
I've got this problem
with duplicate strings.
我有太多的绳子
I've got too many strings.
所以我要你做的就是创造一个函数
So what I need you to do is create
a function that takes a string,
将返回具有重复删除项的新字符串。
returns a new string
with duplicates remove.
因此，我的测试用例是一个测试字符串。
So my test case for this is a test string.
我希望您创建一个函数，以字符串和
And I want you to create a function
that takes in a string and
只会除去所有重复项。
just removes all the duplicates.
所以它应该是一个测试字符串，或者是沿着这些线的东西。
So it should return this is a test string,
or something along those lines.
这个有点棘手，所以我要用十分钟的时间来回答这个问题。
And this one is a little trickier,
so I'll say ten minutes on this one.
还记得我们之前使用过的那些方法，它们在这里会很有帮助。
And remember those methods we used
earlier, they'll be really helpful here.
>> 那么问题，仅适用于
&gt;&gt; So questions, is this only for
这句话是一样的吗
words that are the same that
are next to each other?
或者如果有另一个是在那句里的话
Or if there was another
is in that sentence,
就应该去掉其中的两个，就留一个吧 ?
it should remove two of them and
just leave one?
>> 大问题。
&gt;&gt; Great question.
是的你会问这个问题
Yes, that's a great
question you would ask.
是啊，什么位置都不重要。
Yes, it doesn't matter
what the position is.
它应该只具有一个唯一值。
It should only have one unique value.
实际上，我将调用此唯一值或重复字符串。
In fact I would call this unique values or
duplicate strings.
所以我也可以用数字做同样的事情
So I could do the same thing with numbers
if I wanted to kind of give it a way too
很多是吗
much, yes?
>> 大写为大写，小写为小写，
&gt;&gt; Capitalization matters like
uppercase this and lowercase this,
它们会是同一个字符串还是它们太独特了
would they be the same string or
would they be too unique?
>好的问题我要说他们是独一无二的
&gt;&gt; Good question,
I'm gonna say they're unique but
在解决这个问题上我也不在乎
in terms of solving this
I wouldn't care as much.
但我喜欢这个问题意味着你已经在思考了，对吗 ?
But I love that question that means
you're already thinking ahead, yes?
>> 您是否可以始终除去第一次出现的重复项或
&gt;&gt; Can you always remove the first
occurrence of the duplicate or
你会不会第一次出现然后把东西移走吗
do you leave the first occurrence and
remove the things after that?
>> 大问题，没关系。
&gt;&gt; Great question, it doesn't matter.
这件事更开放了 - >> 这件事我不知道。
This one is more of an open ended-
&gt;&gt; This one it doesn't matter I guess.
> > 是，这是一个更开放的问题。
&gt;&gt; Yeah,
this is more of an open ended question.
我会说这一点
And I'll say this,
一般的采访者大概会给你试镜。
in general the interviewer probably
is gonna give you test cases.
他们会说创建一个函数来执行字符串和
They'll just say create
a function that takes string and
返回已除去重复项的新字符串。
returns a new string
with duplicates removed.
我给你测试是因为我是个好人
I'm giving you test cases
because I'm a nice person, but
如果你在白板上他们可能不会为你那样做
if you're on a whiteboard, they're
probably not gonna do that for you.